Hi guys Welcome to my YouTube vlog for
today's video review of Emer flex
that Emer flex that idc for 100 infrared
ceramic coper 10 kg That's it You can
use this ceramic teflon n
I cooked corn be if it will work
So That's our review
its socket is two flat so you don't
need an
adapter Plug and Play That's it when
you just plug in the power
su Try if
ceramic they say you still need
something compatible but that's okay just
turn on that function
its power how strong is the electricity
1,800 the heat power is adjustable
also included in that function As for
the temperature so 400
Cel maung 400 to 500 Cel That's it's going to get very
hot so be
careful that Wait for it first so let's try
first how will we know If it
has reached that yet it has not
been reported yet
[Music]
How will we know if it has reached that there is
26 CM there 50 to 500 up to 3 hours
timer  You can time it. So
you can leave it. That's it. Once
you get it, it's hot. The
red color will die. That means it's already at 400 Cel. So be
careful. You saw that it can
boil something. So it's
800 power. Temperature is 500. That's it. That's it. It's
very simple. Once
you're done, you can just
melt it. That's it. It's simple. If
you like videos like that, YouTube
channel. Greetings.